[Music]
hi welcome back to my channel so this is
going to be a quick review i usually
review food and drink products on my
channel um but today i thought i'd
change things a little
so
i saw this website um it was popping up
on my facebook ads and checked out the
website it's a company that sell
um biological laundry capsules and
non-biological laundry capsules and also
lots of other products fabric softeners
um i think there's other items i was
selling there as well
mainly for obviously laundry
um
i can't remember if they saw anything
else like for dishes but it was mainly
laundry i could see on that so i signed
up for their free trial i'm going to try
these out today on my video and show you
what i think of the quality of the
product
and yeah i thought it'd be a change it's
a sustainable way apparently an
eco-friendly way
of
having your pods delivered rather than
lots and lots of black packaging
so i usually have this
which is from a supermarket so lots of
pods and fabric softener
it gets a bit frustrating because this
takes up the whole cupboard
and
i usually alternate change around the
pods depending on the week
because some are different scented but
there's a lot of packaging
in fact i've got another bottle of
fabric softener in the cupboard so you
can imagine that's quite a lot i didn't
get the fabric softener from this
company i did get the pots so these are
capsules pods same thing
so i'm going to show you the quality of
the pods pop in the machine show you the
wash cycle show you what the laundry
looks like after
yeah i am going to use some of my own
fabric softener because i didn't buy the
one on their website
but it looks interesting so
let's have a close-up of the pods
so i
i tried to open this
this one
and uh it didn't go too well
so it's obviously a child lock safety
feature on the box which is fair enough
because these can be hazardous to
children
so
i ripped the box a bit but it doesn't
matter i've got i've got another pack as
well but uh yeah so these are the pods
capsules
um as you can see very similar to what
you get in a supermarket
but less plastic
um yeah really happy with these so i'm
gonna pop one in the wash now and let
you know what i think
um so yeah like comment subscribe
have you tried this product before have
you signed up on their website
um have you seen this advertised what do
you think let me know that'd be really
really helpful so i'm gonna pop one of
these in the laundry now and then get
back to you um do some clips obviously
of how it looks in the machine
if it gives a lot of soaps sort of like
foam uh just look at the quality of it
really so let's have a look okay so
we're gonna pop this part under this
laundry the same as i do with the pods
that i get from the supermarket
under the laundry
i've just put a load of microfiber
cloths in here and some tea towels
a bathtub and a hand towel okay so i'm
gonna pop this on and see what the soap
suds are like how it how it breaks down
compared to the pods from a supermarket
give it about 30 seconds to fill up with
water and then we'll see how the pod
breaks down um if it releases like a lot
of soap studs which is always a good
sign
um so yeah
really intrigued to see what the product
quality is like while we're waiting for
the washing machine to fill i just like
to say uh the quality of the cardboard
is excellent for um this being sent in
the post through the letterbox the only
issue like i said just earlier i messed
up opening the box unfortunately i've
never opened one of these before
but i'm sure i won't mess up the other
box but so far machine's filling up and
i'll show you what it's like once it
starts mixing with water wow as you can
see
it's foaming up very well already it's
only just started turning
wow this is good quality quite impressed
in fact
some pods capsules away from the
supermarket
are not effective as this uh wow look at
this quality of the soup i'm impressed
so
we're going to let this do its cycle and
i'll get back to you at the end
to show you once it's spun
um yeah i'm impressed with the quality
so far this has only been on about 20 30
seconds
yeah really good um
just showing a little bit more yeah it's
breaking down really well
i'm impressed by the quality of this
product
wow
very impressed with the quality
at the soap
i only put in one pod as well usually
with a branded
capsule pod
it doesn't have this effect straight
away but this is impressive
it's also quite relaxing to watch your
laundry go around
[Music]
four minutes to go until the end of the
cycle and there's still quite a lot of
soap which is really impressive i've got
to wait for one more rinse and then i
will show you what the laundry looks
like
once all the soap has been rinsed out of
it but i'm really impressed with the
quality
right so let's see how did this turn out
well it smells really nice in here
um yeah everything seems
really clean
yeah really happy with the quality
it's it's but it's a little bit better
than the supermarket one i buy
so yeah very happy i'm going to hang
this up
um i might pop it in the tumble dryer
later as well actually um i like my
towels fluffy um so yeah really happy
with this the quality is good highly
recommended you get a free trial which
is like i think it was a pounder box
which was really good and i got a ton of
pods capsules so yeah really happy the
quality um highly recommended
yep smells absolutely lovely there's
nothing like fresh laundry take care
thank you so much for watching my video
and i'll be uploading again soon bye